A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Overseas Development, International Training and Research, Office Files of John Howard FA608
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1951-1969, bulk 1951-1966; 1951-1966; I
  - Fellowships -- Pakistan Office -- Fellowship Matters -- Correspondence, 1954-1962 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Directory of Foreign Area Training Fellows, 1952-1959 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Ford Fellows in the Foreign Service Evaluation -- State Department Study, 1960-1962 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- H.C.L. Merillat -- Review of Fellowship Program, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Howland Sargeant -- Evaluation of Overseas Training and Research Program -- General File, Recommendations, etc., 1954-1955 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Programs Evaluations, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Farm-Out of Foreign Area Training Fellowship Program to SSRC-ACLS, 1955-1962 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Medical Contingencies of Fellows While Overseas, 1954-1956 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Publications Resulting from Fellowships, 1956-1957 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Recruitment Report -- John M. Thompson, 1954 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Screening Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Screening Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Screening Committee, 1956 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Screening Committee, 1957 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Screening Committee, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Screening Committee, 1959-1969 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Screening Committees (excluding Law Faculty Fellowship Program), 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Foreign Area Training Fellowships Screening Committee Instructions, 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Foreign Area Fellowship Program Screening Committee Instructions, 1964-1965 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Statistics, 1952-1954 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Statistics, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Statistics, 1956 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Statistics, 1957 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Statistics, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Statistics, 1959 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Statistics, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Statistics, 1961 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Fellowship Statistics, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Foreign Area Fellowship Statistics, 1962-1963 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Africa, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Africa, 1956-1957 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Africa, 1958 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Africa, 1959 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Africa, 1960 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Africa, 1961 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Africa, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Asia and the Near East (for earlier years see "General"), 1955 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Asia and the Near East, 1956-1957 (Box 11)
  - Fellowships -- Asia and the Near East, 1958 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Asia and the Near East, 1959 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Asia and the Near East -- Award Letters, 1960 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Asia and the Near East, 1961-1962 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Asia and the Near East, 1962 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Asia and the Near East -- Supplement for Training on Chinese Affairs, 1961-1962 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Asia and the Near East -- William W. Lockwood Report on Fellows Abroad, 1953 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Latin America, 1961 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Latin America, 1962 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Soviet and East European Program -- S.S. Meeting, 1955 December 3 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Soviet and East European Program Area, 1955 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Soviet and East European Program Area, 1956-1957 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Soviet and East European Program Area, 1958 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Soviet and East European Program Area, 1959 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Soviet and East European Program Area -- Award Letters, 1960 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Soviet and East European Program Area, 1961-1962 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- International Relations Training Fellowship Program, 1955-1958 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- "Refresher" Fellowships -- Support for Special Training Needs Under Asia-Near East Fellowship Program, 1955-1958 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Foundation-Administered Project -- Fellowships for Training Relating to Asia and the Near and Middle East, 1956 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Foreign Area Training Fellowship Program -- General -- Grants, 1952-1953 (Box 12)
  - Fellowships -- Foreign Area Training Fellowship Program -- General -- Grants-in-Aid Program --"Farmed-Out" Fellowship Program, 1955-1961 (Box 12)
  - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy -- Tufts University -- General File (incl. photographs), 1957 (Box 13)
  - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy -- Tufts University (L65-76), 1963-1966 (Box 13)
  - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy -- Tufts University (L65-76) -- Attachments -- Atlantic Community Studies Proposal, 1964 January (Box 13)
  - Ford Foundation Programs and Developing Federal Activities, 1965 (Box 13)
  - Ford Foundation -- Memoranda to and from Other Programs, 1963-1965 (Box 13)
  - Ford Foundation -- Staff Relations with Prospective Grantees, 1965 (Box 13)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1961 (Box 13)
  - Foreign Students -- General, 1953-1966 (Box 13)
  - Foreign Students -- "Why Foreign Students" Report by Mr. Fox for Langmuir Committee, 1961 September (Box 13)
  - Foreign Students -- Foreign Student Orientation (PA58-24), 1961 July 31 (Box 13)
  - Fox, Melvin -- Memoranda Re: ITR Activities, International Studies, Workshops, Fellowships, Training Program, 1963-1966 (Box 13)
  - Frankel, Charles -- "The Neglected Aspect of Foreign Affairs: American Educational and Cultural Policy Abroad", 1963-1965 (Box 13)
  - G -- General Files, Correspondence, 1952-1966 (Box 13)
  - Germany -- Berlin -- General Correspondence, 1951-1957 (Box 13)
  - Grants/Fellowships -- Foundation Policy on Rejections, 1952-1965 (Box 13)
  - Grants/Fellowships -- University of Colorado -- International Cooperative Research Project on Conflict Resolution, 1966 (Box 13)
  - Grants/Fellowships -- University of Pennsylvania -- Comparative American Survey and Analysis of Values and Political Decisions (L65-201), 1965 (Box 13)
  - Greece -- General Correspondence, 1951-1958 (Box 13)
  - H -- General Correspondence, 1952-1966 (Box 13)
  - Harvard University -- General, 1957-1965 (Box 13)
  - Harvard -- Conference on Cultural Aid to Underdeveloped Areas (August 1-3, 1960), 1960-1961 (Box 13)
  - Harvard -- Program of National Defense Studies, 1955 (Box 13)
  - Harvard -- Public Health Role of University in International Health, 1961-1962 (Box 13)
  - Hawaii -- General Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 13)
  - Hawaii -- General Correspondence, 1954-1958 (Box 14)
  - Hawaii -- General Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 14)
  - Hawaii, University of -- The East-West Center, 1959-1964 (Box 14)
  - Hawaii, University of -- International Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 14)
  - Heussler, Robert -- Memoranda Re: Latin American Studies and Fellowships, 1963-1964 (Box 14)
  - Historical Evaluation and Research Organization (HERO) -- Projects, 1963 (Box 14)
  - Honolulu Academy of Arts -- Bishop Museum Proposal, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
  - I -- General Files, Correspondence, Reports, etc., 1951-1966 (Box 14)
  - India -- General, 1956-1960 (Box 14)
  - India -- General -- Reports, Notes, etc., 1952-1959 (Box 14)
  - India -- General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 14)
  - India -- General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 14)
  - India -- Program in Monetary Economics -- University of Bombay -- Alvin Hansen (PA57-192), 1956-1960 (Box 14)
  - Indiana University -- General File, 1957-1960 (Box 14)
  - Indiana University -- Background Material Long-Term Support (61-160), 1960-1963 (Box 14)
  - Indiana and Notre Dame Universities -- Proposed Exchange -- Poland, 1959-1960 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- General -- Reports, Correspondence, 1952-1960 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- Education in Indonesia, circa 1955-1956 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- Field Research Problems in Indonesia (Peter Goethals), 1957 June 23 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- General Correspondence, 1952 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- General Correspondence, 1953 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- General Correspondence, 1954 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- General Correspondence, 1955 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- General Correspondence, 1956 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- General Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- General Correspondence, 1959 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- General Correspondence Incl. List of Grants Made between 1952 and 1954, 1960 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- Grant Requests, 1954 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- List of Books on Indonesia, 1955 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- Personnel Post Report (ICA Post Report), 1956 January (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- Public Administration -- Dean Litchfield, 1953-1954 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- Summary of Program for 1956-1957 -- Status Report, 1959 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia -- Technical Teacher Training Program (53-113, also 53-23) -- Dunwoody Institute, 1953-1956 (Box 14)
  - Indonesia, University of -- Dean Djokosutono -- National Police (L4-1695), 1954-1958 (Box 14)
  - Indonesian English Language Teaching Projects (Various), 1952-1958 (Box 14)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE), 1964-1965 (Box 15)
  - Institute for Policy Studies -- Seminars on Alliance for Progress -- IA Program Grant (PA 64-127), 1962-1965 (Box 15)
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1951-1961 (Box 15)
  - International Association of Universities-UNESCO -- Study of Facilities for Higher Education in Southeast Asia (L 60-1034), 1959-1964 (Box 15)
  - International Economic Development, 1956-1961 (Box 15)
  - International Institute for Educational Planning -- Philip H. Coombs, 1963-1965 (Box 15)
  - International Relations -- Conferences on the Teaching of International Relations -- Richard Snyder, 1956 (Box 15)
  - International Relations Review Meeting, 1958 February 12 (Box 15)
  - International Relations -- Teaching of IR (Mr. Merillat's file) -- Conferences, Proposals, Correspondence, Reports, 1955-1958 (Box 15)
  - International Studies in American College Education and International Relations Programs, 1953-1957 (Box 15)
  - International Studies -- Consultants on International Studies (non-Western) in Undergraduate Education -- Berger, Coppock, Elliot, 1962-1965 (Box 15)
  - International Studies -- Consultants on International Studies (non-Western) in Undergraduate Education -- Gil, Hucker, Whitman, 1962-1963 (Box 15)
  - International Studies -- Meeting on International Studies (non-Western) in Undergraduate Education at Ford Foundation (L 8-576), 1958 July 10 (Box 15)
  - International Studies -- Meeting on International Studies (non-Western) in Undergraduate Education at Indiana University, 1958 September 18-20 (Box 15)
  - International Studies -- Meeting on International Studies (non-Western) in Undergraduate Education at Ford Foundation (L 60-735), 1960 December 5 (Box 15)
  - International Studies -- Meeting on International Studies (non-Western) in Undergraduate Education at Ford Foundation (L 61-54), 1961 February 16 (Box 15)
  - International Studies (non-Western) in the Undergraduate Curriculum -- Retraining Faculty, 1961 (Box 15)
  - International Studies (non-Western) in the Undergraduate Curriculum -- Williams College, 1963-1964 (Box 15)
  - International Studies (non-Western) in the Undergraduate Curriculum -- General (folder 1), 1958-1966 (Box 15)
  - International Studies (non-Western) in the Undergraduate Curriculum -- General (folder 2), 1958-1966 (Box 15)
  - International Studies (non-Western) in the Undergraduate Curriculum -- General (folder 3), 1958-1966 (Box 15)
  - International Studies -- Reports Re: Ford Foundation Missions to Asia, Possible Ford Foundation Activities in the Philippines, and Working Party on Near East, 1952-1957 (Box 15)
  - Inter-University Consortium for Political Research -- Philip Converse (L63-259), 1963 (Box 16)
  - Inter-University Committee on Travel Grants (61-105), 1960-1961 (Box 16)
  - Inter-University Committee on Travel Grants -- Indiana and Columbia Universities (61-105), 1957-1959 (Box 16)
  - Italy -- General Correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 16)
  - J -- General Files, 1961-1963 (Box 16)
  - Japan -- Conference on Urbanization in Japan Held in Carmel, CA, 1959 August 11-17 (Box 16)
  - Japan -- John Scott Everton Trip to Japan -- Documents Used in Preparation for Trip (1957), 1955-1957 (Box 16)
  - Japan -- John S. Everton Trip to Japan (1957), 1957-1958 (Box 16)
  - Japan -- General Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 16)
  - Japan -- General Correspondence, 1954 (Box 16)
  - Japan -- General Correspondence, 1955 (Box 16)
  - Japan -- General Correspondence, 1956 (Box 16)
  - Japan -- General Correspondence, 1957 (Box 16)
  - Japan -- General Correspondence, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Japan -- General Correspondence, 1959 (Box 16)
  - Japan -- General Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 16)
  - Japan -- ITR Program -- Relation to Other Programs, Everton 1961 Review, etc., 1960-1963 (Box 16)
  - Japan -- Japanese-American Relations, Conference on -- Held in Princeton, 1952 November (Box 16)
  - Japan -- "Japan and the Philippines" -- George Taylor Report, 1952 (Box 16)
  - K -- General Files, 1952-1966 (Box 16)
  - Kentucky, University of -- Training Program in Developmental Change (L 64-8), 1964 (Box 16)
  - Kluckhohn, Florence R. -- Methods of Testing Value Orientation Theory (L 63-988), 1964 (Box 17)
  - Korean Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 17)
  - L -- General Files, 1952-1966 (Box 17)
  - Language Development -- General, 1963-1965 (Box 17)
  - Language Development -- National Defense Education Act, 1961-1962 (Box 17)
  - Language Development -- Proposed Appropriation for Critical Foreign Languages, 1960 (Box 17)
  - Language Development -- World Language Survey, 1962 (Box 17)
  - Latin America Studies -- Conference on Area Studies, Latin American Programs held at the Plaza Hotel, 1963 January 18 (Box 17)
  - Latin America Studies -- Draft Spaeth Survey Reports, 1963 (Box 17)
  - Latin America Studies -- Harvard University, 1961-1964 (Box 17)
  - Latin America Studies -- International Study Center, Inc. -- Richard H. Stephens (L65-171), 1965 (Box 17)
  - Latin America Studies -- William S. Barnes Re: Proposal for Teaching and Research in Inter-American Affairs in the New England Area (L63-870), 1964-1965 (Box 17)
  - M -- General Files, 1952-1966 (Box 17)
  - MIT -- Labor Relations Research Program in India -- Myers, Charles, 1957 (Box 17)
  - MIT, Harvard, University of Chicago and University of California -- Joint Research in Use of Human Resources -- Study of Labor as Factor in Economic Development (54-19), 1954 (Box 17)
  - Michigan State University -- General, 1958-1963 (Box 17)
  - Michigan State University -- Regional Meeting at MSU -- Committee on Regent Responsiblity for University Participation in Education Abroad, 1961 October 5-6 (Box 17)
  - Michigan, University of -- General, 1961-1964 (Box 17)
  - Michigan Universities Consortium -- General File, 1966 (Box 17)
  - Minnesota, University of -- General, 1960-1962 (Box 17)
  - N -- General Files, Correspondence, 1951-1964 (Box 17)
  - National University Extension Association Committee on World Affairs Meetings in Washington, 1960 November 11-12 (Box 17)
  - Near East -- American University at Cairo, 1952-1963 (Box 17)
  - Near East -- American University of Beirut, 1951-1964 (Box 17)
  - Near East -- Financial Reports, General, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Near East -- General Correspondence, 1953 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- General Correspondence, 1954 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- General Correspondence, 1955 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- General Correspondence, 1956 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- General Correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- General Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Harvey Hall Proposal -- Research Centers in Arab States, 1952-1954 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Iran, 1952-1956 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Iraq, 1953-1955 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Israel, 1953-1958 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Jordan, 1953-1956 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Lebanon, 1953-1954 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Mission, May 1952 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Press Release, 1952 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Reed, Howard -- Program Specialist in Training and Research, 1952-1958 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Regional, 1953-1954 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- "Report of the Working Party on the Near East", undated (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Reports, 1953 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Reports, 1954 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Saudi Arabia, 1953 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Special Education Program for Arab States (Victor Butterfield Report), 1953-1957 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Syria, 1953-1954 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Training and Research Program -- General File (see also Howard Reed file) (L6-472), 1955-1958 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Turkey, 1953-1959 (Box 18)
  - Near East -- Turkey -- University of Istanbul -- Institute of Business Administration, 1953-1956 (Box 18)
  - Negro Education, 1963-1965 (Box 18)
  - New York University -- Gould House Conference on International Education, 1960 January (Box 18)
  - New York University -- Miscellaneous, 1954-1962 (Box 18)
  - New York, University of the State of -- General, 1960-1963 (Box 18)
  - O -- General, 1963 (Box 18)
  - Ohio State University -- Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 18)
  - Oregon, University of, 1962 (Box 18)
  - Organization for Tropical Studies -- Jay Savage (L64-227), 1963-1966 (Box 18)
  - Overseas Development Program -- Reports, General, 1954-1960 (Box 18)
  - Overseas Representatives -- First Conference -- Beirut, 1953 October 6-8 (Box 18)
  - Overseas Representatives -- Second Conference -- New York, 1954 March 1 (Box 18)
  - Overseas Representatives -- Third Conference -- New York, 1955 March 17 (Box 18)
  - Overseas Representatives -- Third Conference -- Black Book, 1955 March (Box 18)
  - Overseas Representatives -- Fourth Conference -- New York, 1956 October (Box 19)
  - Overseas Service -- Personnel Matters -- Policies and Procedures, 1954-1958 (Box 19)
  - Overseas Service -- Training Americans for Overseas Service -- Conference Papers -- Princeton (L7-741), 1960 November 3-5 (Box 19)
  - Overseas Service -- Training, 1953 (Box 19)
  - Overseas Service -- Training, 1960-1961 (Box 19)
  - Overseas Service -- Training, 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Oxford University -- St. Anthony's College (Oxford) -- Development of Programs in East European and Asian Studies -- IA Grant (PA 59-173), 1958-1959 (Box 19)
  - P -- General Files, 1955-1966 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- Domestic Science -- Home Economics Program, 1952-1955 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- Education Program, 1953-1958 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- General, 1953-1958 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- General Correspondence, 1951 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- General Correspondence, 1952 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- General Correspondence, 1953 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- General Correspondence, 1954 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- General Correspondence, 1955 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- General Correspondence, 1956 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- General Correspondence, 1957 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- General Correspondence, 1958 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- General Correspondence, 1959 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- Grant Requests, 1954 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- National Planning Board -- Development of a Five Year Plan, 1957 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- Polytechnic Training Institute -- Industrial Training Centers, 1951-1954 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- Public Administration, 1953-1958 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- Report on Social Science Research in Pakistan by Moeen Qureshi, 1954 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- Reports, 1953 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- Reports, 1954 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- Social Science Research Institute, 1954-1955 (Box 19)
  - Pakistan -- Village Development Program, 1951-1954 (Box 19)
  - Pennsylvania State University -- General File, 1958-1963 (Box 20)
  - Personnel -- Study of the Availability of Personnel for Overseas Assignment (Gant-Sanders) (PA 62-449), 1962 (Box 20)
  - Personnel -- Proposed Overseas Development Study of Personnel for Overseas Development (Hilliard), 1955-1963 (Box 20)
  - Philippines -- General Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 20)
  - Philippines -- General Correspondence, 1954-1962 (Box 20)
  - Pittsburgh, University of, 1958-1963 (Box 20)
  - Population -- American Committee, International Union for Research and Population (World Population Conference 1954), 1953-1958 (Box 20)
  - Princeton University -- General, 1958-1963 (Box 20)
  - Princeton University -- Long-Term Support -- Background Materials (61-362), 1961 (Box 20)
  - Princeton University -- Stanley J. Stein, History Department, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
  - Professional Education Program -- Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 20)
  - Program Directors' Meetings, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
  - Public Affairs -- General, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
  - Purdue University -- Program of International Studies in Rural Development (L63-770), 1963-1965 (Box 20)
  - R -- General Files, 1952-1966 (Box 20)
  - Rabinowitz, Richard -- Personnel Component in Transcultural Affairs, 1960 (Box 20)
  - Randolph-Macon -- Proposed Exchange with India, 1963 (Box 20)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1956-1961 (Box 20)
  - S -- General Files, 1951-1966 (Box 20)
  - Slavic Studies -- Joint Committee on Slavic Studies, 1957-1958 (Box 20)
  - Social Science Research Council -- General File, 1955-1966 (Box 20)
  - Social Science Research Council -- Ten Year Grant for General Support (PA 56-140A), 1961 (Box 20)
  - Southern California, University of, 1956-1961 (Box 20)
  - Southern California, University of (L63-268 and later PA 63-413), 1964 (Box 20)
  - Southern California, University of -- Soviet-Asian Studies -- R. Swearingen, 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - Southern California, University of -- Study of Communist Education (Theodore H.E. Chen), 1963-1965 (Box 20)
  - Stanford University -- Comparative Education Program, 1960-1961 (Box 20)
  - Stanford University -- General, 1955-1964 (Box 21)
  - Stanford University -- Hoover Institute and Library -- General, 1955-1963 (Box 21)
  - Syracuse University -- Maxwell School -- General, 1957-1964 (Box 21)
  - T -- General Files, 1952-1966 (Box 21)
  - Teachers College (Columbia University) -- Program on International Education, 1957-1961 (Box 21)
  - Texas, University of, 1962 (Box 21)
  - Thailand, 1955-1961 (Box 21)
  - Technical Assistance Programs Incl. Report "Agricultural Credit in Selected Countries of Asia and the Near East with Suggestions for Activities to Improve Credit for Farmers" by V. Webster Johnson and Edwin C. Johnson, 1953-1965 (Box 21)
  - Thurber, Clarence -- General File -- Various Research Projects, Ideas, Memoranda on Proposals, etc., 1954-1962 (Box 21)
  - Thurber, Clarence -- Memoranda, Reports Re: International Training and Development, ITR Work, 1953-1962 (Box 21)
  - Tibetan Studies, 1959-1961 (Box 21)
  - Training of Foreign Nationals -- Africa, 1954-1955 (Box 21)
  - Training of Foreign Nationals -- Burma, 1955 (Box 21)
  - Training of Foreign Nationals -- General, 1955-1964 (Box 21)
  - Training of Foreign Nationals -- India, 1955 (Box 21)
  - Training of Foreign Nationals -- Indonesia, 1955 (Box 21)
  - Training of Foreign Nationals -- William C. Johnstone, Jr., 1955 (Box 21)
  - Training of Foreign Nationals -- Near East, 1955-1957 (Box 21)
  - Training of Foreign Nationals -- Pakistan, 1955 (Box 21)
  - Tufts University, 1960-1961 (Box 21)
  - Tyner, Richard -- General File, 1965 (Box 21)
  - U -- General Files, 1951-1966 (Box 21)
  - UNESCO -- General Correspondence Re: UNESCO, 1951-1960 (Box 21)